Finding aid for the J. Paul Getty Museum, Getty Villa Construction Records, 1960, 1964, 1968-1986 and undated (bulk 1971-1974) IA10001
Institutional Records and Archives
- Reports, 1968-1974; Series II.; 2.1 Linear Feet (5 boxes)
  - Reports from Stephen Garrett, 1968-1973; Series II.B.; 1.25 Linear Feet (3 boxes)
    - Report #4, January 9, 1970 (Box 1986.IA.08-04, Folder 11)
      [File also includes 2 untitled memos, February 19, 1970; "Summary of Decisions made by Mr. Getty...," March 20, 1970; "Check and Discuss," March 25, 1970; "Background Information relating to Decisions made by Mr. Getty...;" March 25, 1970 .]
    - Report #5, April 6, 1970 (Box 1986.IA.08-04, Folder 12)
      [File also contains correspondence from Stephen Garrett to J. Paul Getty, re. Decisions on Report #5, April 10, 1970 .]
    - Report #6, April 16, 1970 (Box 1986.IA.08-04, Folder 13)
    - Report #7, April 17, 1970 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 1)
      [File also contains "Typical Queries arising out of proposal to reconstruct the Villa dei Papiri...," May 11, 1970 .]
    - Report #8, June 3, 1970 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 2)
      [File also contains correspondence from Stephen Garrett to J. Paul Getty, re. Decisions on Report #8, June 5, 1970 .]
    - Report #9, June 12, 1970
      - Papers, June 12, 1970 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 3)
      - Oversize, June 12, 1970 (Flatfile 1986.IA.08-37)
    - Report #10, August 11, 1970 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 4)
    - Report #11, December 23, 1970 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 5)
      [Includes memo "Notes on meeting held at Sutton Place...," December 14, 1970.]
    - Report #12 –, January 14, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 6)
      [Includes memo "Notes on decisions made by Mr. Getty...," January 28, 1971.]
    - Report #13, March 15, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 7)
      [Includes memos "Matters discussed and agreed at meeting...," March 5, 1971; "Notes on matters discussed...," March 8, 1971; untitled memo from Stephen Garrett to J. Paul Getty, March 11, 1971; and "Notes on meeting..."]
    - Report #14, March 28, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 8)
      [File also includes "Film," March 31, 1971 with attached telegram April 8, 1971; memos to file from Frank Whitworth, April 7 and 8, 1971; "Matters for discussion at next visit" (undated); and untitled memo from Stephen Garrett to Norris Bramlett, March 3, 1971.]
    - Report #15, April 12, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 9)
      [File also contains attached correspondence from Robert Langdon to Norris Bramlett (April 18, 1971); from T. W. Smith (Dinwiddie) to Langdon & Wilson (April 8, 1971); from unknown to Norman Neuerburg (March 30, 1971); and "Notes by Dr Neuerburg – Gallery 14 Hercules Room" – April 14, 1971 with photocopied diagrams.]
    - Report #16, April 15, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 10)
      [The file also includes the memo "Notes on telephone conversation...," April 23, 1971.]
    - Report #17, April 30, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 11)
      [The file also contains the memos "Notes on various details...," July 12, 1971 and "Notes on decisions reached and comments made...," July 26, 1971.]
    - Report #18, August 18, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 12)
      [The file also contains correspondence from T. W. Smith (Dinwiddie) to Langdon & Wilson (August 4, 1971, and Aug 5, 1971); "West Garden" – undated (circa August 1971); and "Reports" – August 18, 1971 (listing of Stephen Garrett reports).]
    - Report #19, August 23, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 13)
    - Report #20, September 6, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 13)
    - Report #21, September 20, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 14)
    - Report #22, October 7, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 14)
    - Report #23, October 25, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 14)
    - Report #24, November 19, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 15)
      [The file also contains "Matters for discussion...," November 19, 1971.]
    - Report #25, December 8, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 16)
      [The file also contains correspondence from T. W. Smith (Dinwiddie) to Langdon & Wilson (August 5, 1971), T.W. Smith to Norris Bramlett (December 1 and 2, 1971), Emmet Wemple to Stephen Garrett (November 29 and December 1, 1971), and Norman Neuerburg to Stephen Garrett (September 19, 1971). Also unattributed memos entitled "Climate Control J. P. Getty Museum," "Fire Protection Systems – Getty Museum," "Security System Resume," and "Lighting of the Main Floor of the Museum."]
    - Report #26, December 13, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 17)
    - Report #27, December 29, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 17)
    - Report #28, January 7, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-05, Folder 17)
    - Report #29, February 23, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 1)
    - Report #30, February 28, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 2)
    - Report #31, March 13, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 2)
    - Report #32, April 18, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 2)
    - Report #33, June 8, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 3)
      [With attached correspondence from Stephen Garrett to Norris Bramlett, June 16, 1972.]
    - Report #34, June 16, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 4)
    - Report #35, July 4, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 4)
    - Report #36, July 21, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 5)
    - Report #37, July 21, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 6)
      [File also contains "Proposed design for Ceiling to West Porch" – August 8, 1972.]
    - Report 37a, "Galleries – Preliminary Schedule of Design and Contents,", August 9, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 6)
    - Report #38, August 29, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 6)
    - Report #39, September 15, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 7)
      [File also contains untitled memo from Stephen Garrett –September 25, 1972 and "Notes on designed submitted by Langdon & Wilson..." – .]
    - Report #40, September 27, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 8)
    - Report #41, October 11, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 8)
    - Report #42, October 30, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 8)
      [The file also contains correspondence from Stephen Garrett to J. Paul Getty – October 30, 1972 and "Villa Dei Papiri: proposed excavations" – October 30, 1972.]
    - Report #43, November 10, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 9)
    - Report #44, November 14, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 10)
    - Report #45, December 19, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 10)
    - Report #46, January 17, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 10)
    - Report #47, January 25, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 11)
    - Report #48, February 26, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 11)
    - Report #49, March 8, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 11)
    - Report #50, April 4, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-06, Folder 12)
    - Report #51, April 4, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 1)
    - Report #52, April 8, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 1)
      [The file also contains "Signs – Comment on John Follis & Associates Proposals..." – April 25, 1973.]
    - Report #53, May 4, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 2)
    - Report #54, May 18, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 3)
      [The file also contains "Progress: as reported in a letter from Norman Neuerburg..." - May 8, 1973.]
    - Report #55, July 10, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 3)
    - Report #56, July 10, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 4)
    - Report #57, July 13, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 4)
    - Report #58, July 13, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 4)
    - Report #59, August 7, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 5)
    - Report #60, August 8, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 6)
      [The file also contains "Matters discussed and agreed between Mr. Getty, Mr. Bramlett and Mr. Garrett..." – December 3, 1973.]
  - Reports from architects and consultants, 1970-1974; Series II.C.; 0.63 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
    These are arranged chronologically. Two copies of the majority of the Bulletins have been preserved.
    The records consist of reports, with some accompanying memoranda, correspondence, articles, clippings, and notes, dating 1970-1974, that were created by Langdon & Wilson and various contractors to record the progress of the construction of the Villa Museum. The reports were sent to Getty, Norris Bramlett, and Stephen Garrett. Some of the reports record the construction status and responses to specific construction questions.
    The majority of the reports were written by Langdon & Wilson, who produced the "Specifications for Construction of the J. Paul Getty Museum" in December 1970 and followed up with a series of Bulletins that served as amendments or supplements to the original document. The first report details the original construction specifications while the Bulletins describe later revisions and additions.
    - Reports, memos, and construction schedules, 1970-1972; 1974 (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 7)
      [Includes correspondence from Langdon & Wilson, Brandow & Johnson Associates, Dr. Norman Neuerburg, Emmet Wemple, Standard Cabinet Works, Inc., and Ades Engineering Co.]
    - Reports and research, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 8)
      [Done at the request of J. Paul Getty by Norman Neuerburg and Anna Hladka (?) re. other recreations of Roman Villas. Includes a monograph (first draft), entitled "Ancient marbles and their use in the J. Paul Getty Museum," unsigned but apparently by Neuerburg. Also includes related articles and clippings. ]
    - Langdon and Wilson, Specifications for Construction of the J. Paul Getty Museum, December 9, 1970 (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 9)
      [With handwritten notes (photocopy).]
    - Bulletin No. 1 to Specifications for Construction of the J. Paul Getty Museum, February 11, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 10)
    - Bulletin No. 2, June 2, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 11)
    - Bulletin No. 2, June 2, 1971; (duplicate copy) (Box 1986.IA.08-07, Folder 12)
    - Bulletin No. 3, January 6, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-08, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin No. 4, February 8, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-08, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin No. 5, April 5, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-08, Folder 2)
    - Bulletin No. 6, May 2, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-08, Folder 2)
    - Bulletin No. 7, May 8, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-08, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin No. 8, June 16, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-08, Folder 4)
    - Bulletin No. 9, June 27, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-08, Folder 5)
    - Bulletin No. 10, July 6, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-08, Folder 6)
    - Bulletin No. 11, September 20, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-08, Folder 6)
    - Bulletin No. 12, October 30, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-08, Folder 6)
    - Bulletin No. 13, December 1, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-08, Folder 7)
    - Bulletin No. 14, July 19, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-08, Folder 7)
    - Bulletin No. 15, August 1, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-08, Folder 8)
    - Bulletin No. 16, August 10, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-08, Folder 9)
    - Bulletin No. 17, August 13, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-08, Folder 10)
- Legal documents, 1968-1975; Series III.; 0.25 Linear Feet (1 box)
  Agreements and contracts are followed by permits and permissions.
  Records comprise contracts, correspondence, drafts, amendments, notes, memoranda, permits, deeds, oversize plans, and a bond, dating 1968-1975, relating to the construction of the J. Paul Getty Museum (Villa). The materials document various permits, permissions, and inspections required by the City of Los Angeles, performance bond taken out with Seaboard Surety Company, lists of materials guarantees and warranties, and contracts with the consultants and companies. The bulk of the materials are photocopies.
  - Langdon and Wilson agreement and drafts, 1969 (Box 1986.IA.08-11, Folder 6)
  - Dinwiddie agreement and amendments, 1970; 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-11, Folder 7)
    [The original copy of the contract is not present.]
  - Norman Neuerburg consulting agreement, 1970-1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-11, Folder 8)
    [Includes drafts and correspondence re. the agreement, consulting, and consulting fees ]
  - Guarantees and warranties, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-11, Folder 9)
    [File includes correspondence and memoranda from Dinwiddie Construction Co.]
  - Seaboard Surety Company, performance bonds, 1970-1974 (Box 1986.IA.08-11, Folder 10)
  - Building permits/permissions, 1970-1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-11, Folder 11)
  - Permits from City of Los Angeles, 1970-1974 (Box 1986.IA.08-11, Folder 12)
  - Permits from City of Los Angeles, 1971-1973
    - Papers, 1971-1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-11, Folder 13)
    - Oversize, 1971-1973 (Flatfile 1986.IA.08-37)
  - Permits from City of Los Angeles, 1971-1975 (Box 1986.IA.08-11, Folder 14)
  - Permits from City of Los Angeles, public street easement, 1968 (Box 1986.IA.08-11, Folder 15)
- Architect and consultant budgets, 1968-1976; Series IV.; 0.41 Linear Feet (1 box)
  Stephen Garret's and Norman Neuerburg's files appear first, followed by Langdon & Wilson estimates and invoices, mural and landscaping estimates, Decorative Arts gallery files, and an estimated Villa budget.
  Documents include correspondence, budget estimates, invoices, expense summaries, and memoranda, dating 1968-1975, that record the budget estimates, invoices and expenses of the architects, consultants and vendors who worked on the J. Paul Getty Museum (Villa) construction project. Individuals and firms that figure prominently include Stephen Garrett, Norman Neuerburg, Langdon & Wilson, Garth Benton, and Emmet Wemple. Files dealing with the Decorative Arts galleries originated from the office of Gillian Wilson, the Curator of Decorative Arts.
  - Stephen Garrett, invoices and receipts, 1968-1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-12, Folder 9)
  - Norman Neuerburg, invoices/correspondence re. fees, 1970-1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-12, Folder 10)
  - Langdon and Wilson, projected expenses, February 11, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-12, Folder 2)
  - Langdon and Wilson, invoices, 1969-1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-12, Folder 11)
  - Langdon and Wilson, invoices, 1974-1975 (Box 1986.IA.08-12, Folder 12)
  - Langdon and Wilson, certificates of payment, 1970-1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-13, Folder 1)
  - Garth Benton, Emmet Wemple, mural and landscaping estimates, November 29, 1971; December 1, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-12, Folder 3)
  - Decorative arts galleries, budgets and vendors:
    - Massed estimates calculations, 1972-1973 (Box 2009.IA.28-1)
    - New York vendors, 1972-1973 (Box 2009.IA.28-1)
    - Paris vendors, 1972-1973 (Box 2009.IA.28-1)
    - Los Angeles vendors, 1973-1974 (Box 2009.IA.28-1)
    - Derelian, panelled room estimates, 1973-1974 (Box 2009.IA.28-1)
  - Estimated Villa budget, 1974 (Box 1986.IA.08-12, Folder 1)
- Dinwiddie Construction Company records, 1970-1975; Series V.; 6.9 Linear Feet (18.5 boxes)
  Series V.A. Minutes and meeting supporting documentation, 1971-1973
  Series V.B. Schedules and diaries, 1970-1974
  Series V.C. Billings and expenditures, 1970-1975.
  Records consist of minutes, memoranda, notes, job diaries, drafts, schedules, financial documents, budgets, billing statements, certificates of payment, receipts, invoices, correspondence, graphical charts, and estimates, dating 1970-1975, that track the involvement of and work performed by the Dinwiddie Construction Co. on the J. Paul Getty Museum (Villa) construction project.
  The minutes and supporting documentation summarize meetings held by Dinwiddie Construction Co. and attended by various contractors and consultants to discuss the progress and status of various aspects of the Villa construction project. The job diaries are forms filled out and signed by the Dinwiddie site superintendent on a daily basis to document the ongoing construction activities and the number of workmen employed at the Villa site. The schedules record the anticipated (and revised) plans for construction of the Villa and installation of various building components. The budget and billing files were submitted by Dinwiddie to estimate and document construction and payroll costs incurred while working on the Villa.
  - Minutes and meeting supporting documentation, 1971-1973; Series V.A.; 0.3 Linear Feet (1 box)
    The meeting minutes are listed in numerical and chronological order. A separate file of "State of the Job" reports appears at the end.
    Records consist of minutes, memoranda, notes, drafts, and schedules, dating 1971-1973, that summarize meetings held by Dinwiddie Construction Co. and attended by various contractors and consultants to discuss the progress and status of various aspects of the J. Paul Getty Museum (Villa) construction project. The meeting attendees often, but not always, include representatives from the Getty Museum (Stephen Garrett, Norris Bramlett, Burton Fredericksen, and Gillian Wilson). Accompanying some of the minutes are brief "State of the Job" reports, listing the status of all parts of the construction, as of the date of the document, for the purpose of determining areas that may need special attention from the contractors, designers, and/or the owner to ensure that the completion dates are met. Very rarely, revised construction schedules are attached to the minutes. Some minutes are annotated. Interspersed with the job meeting minutes are minutes from smaller meetings held to discuss marble installation and the finishing schedule.
    Subjects of the meetings include numerous issues with the mechanical aspects of the Villa (transformer vaults, sewer plans, etc.), the scheduling of various construction activities (such as pouring concrete and painting), lighting decisions, reviewing samples of building materials, road improvements, bids, permits, variances, fire suppression, and other construction details.
    - Dinwiddie job meetings:
      - No. 1-10:, August 24, 1971-November 30, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-09, Folder 2)
      - No. 11-20:, December 14, 1971-April 25, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-09, Folder 3)
      - No. 21-30:, May 9, 1972-August 22, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-09, Folder 4)
      - No. 31-40:, September 5, 1972-January 9, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-09, Folder 5)
      - No. 41-45, State of Job Reports:, January 22, 1973-March 27, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-09, Folder 6)
      - No. 46-50, State of Job Reports:, April 10, 1973-June 5, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-09, Folder 7)
      - No. 51-55, State of Job Reports:, June 19, 1973-August 14, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-09, Folder 8)
      - No. 56-60, State of Job Reports:, August 21, 1973-September 25, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-09, Folder 9)
      - No. 61-65, memos:, October 2, 1973-October 30, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-09, Folder 10)
      - No. 66-70:, November 6, 1973-December 18, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-09, Folder 11)
    - Dinwiddie memos, State of the Job Reports:, March-April 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-10, Folder 2)
  - Schedules and job diaries, 1970-1974; Series V.B.; 1.04 Linear Feet (3 boxes)
    The schedules appear first, followed by the job diaries. The diaries are in reverse chronological order within each file.
    Records comprise job diaries, schedules, memoranda, and notes, that range in date from 1970 to 1974. The diaries, the bulk of the material, are forms filled out and signed by the site superintendent on a daily basis to document the ongoing construction activities and the number of workmen employed at the Villa site. The schedules record the anticipated (and revised) plans for construction of the Villa and installation of various building components.
    - Marble Schedules:, March 28, 1973; undated (Box 1986.IA.08-10, Folder 1)
    - Dinwiddie job diaries:
      - December 21, 1970-March 31, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-10, Folder 3)
      - April 1-June 30, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-10, Folder 4)
      - July 1-September 30, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-10, Folder 5)
      - October 1-December 31, 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-10, Folder 6)
      - January 1-March 31, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-10, Folder 7)
      - April 1-June 30, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-10, Folder 8)
      - July 1-September 30, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-10, Folder 9)
      - October 1-December 31, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-10, Folder 10)
      - January 1-March 31, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-10, Folder 11)
      - April 1-June 30, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-10, Folder 12)
      - July 1-September 30, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-11, Folder 1)
      - October 1-December 31, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-11, Folder 2)
      - January 1-April 1974 (Box 1986.IA.08-11, Folder 3)
      - August 28-November 30, 1973, [duplicates] (Box 1986.IA.08-11, Folder 4)
      - December 1, 1973-February 28, 1974, [duplicates] (Box 1986.IA.08-11, Folder 5)
  - Budgets and billings, 1970-1975; Series V.C.; 6.25 Linear Feet (15 boxes)
    Estimates, expenditures, billing totals, and summary sheets are followed by billing and payroll documents.
    Financial documents, budgets, billing statements, certificates of payment, receipts, correspondence, memoranda, graphical charts, and estimates, dating 1970-1975, comprise the budget and billing files submitted by Dinwiddie Construction Company to estimate and document construction and payroll costs incurred while working on the J. Paul Getty Museum (Villa). The majority of the records are made up of formerly bound groupings of Dinwiddie subcontractor billing and payroll documents.
    - Estimates and invoices:
      - Dinwiddie estimates/summary sheets, 1971-1972
        - Papers, 1971-1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-12, Folder 4)
        - Oversize, 1971-1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-30, Folder 1)
      - Dinwiddie estimates/summary sheets, 1972
        - Papers, 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-12, Folder 5)
          [Oversized item has been rehoused into 1986.IA.08-37]
        - Oversize, 1972 (Flatfile 1986.IA.08-37)
      - Dinwiddie estimates/summary sheets, 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-12, Folder 7)
      - Dinwiddie estimates/job cost reports – correspondence re. costs, January-March 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-12, Folder 8)
      - Dinwiddie expenditure statements, February 1972-February 1973 (Box 1986.IA.08-13, Folder 2)
      - Dinwiddie expenditure statements, March 1971-January 1972 (Box 1986.IA.08-13, Folder 3)
      - Dinwiddie expenditure statements, March 1973-December 1974 (Box 1986.IA.08-13, Folder 4)
      - Dinwiddie / subcontractor billing totals, 1974 (Box 1986.IA.08-13, Folder 5)
      - Dinwiddie summaries / subcontractor billing totals, 1971-1974 (Box 1986.IA.08-13, Folder 6)
        [Oversize pages need to be rehoused]
      - Dinwiddie final account, 1974-1975 (Box 1986.IA.08-13, Folder 7)
        [potential legal issue is discussed - confidential??]
      - Dinwiddie: summary sheets, purchase orders, subcontractor invoices, 1972-1974 (Box 1986.IA.08-13, Folder 8)
      - Dinwiddie: summary sheets, purchase orders, subcontractor invoices, 1973-1975 (Box 1986.IA.08-13, Folder 9)
      - Dinwiddie: summary sheets, purchase orders, subcontractor invoices, 1973-1974 (Box 1986.IA.08-14, Folder 1)
      - Dinwiddie: summary sheets, purchase orders, 1973-1974 (Box 1986.IA.08-14, Folder 2)
    - Dinwiddie/Subcontractor billing and payroll:
      [Contains numerous oversize pages - not sure the records really warrant the time and effort it would take to rehouse them, though. Some invoices and receipts are on poor quality paper and the ink is fading/bleeding - same time and effort v. worth issue, though.]
      - December 1970 (Box 1986.IA.08-14, Folder 3)
      - January 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-14, Folder 4)
      - February 1971 (Box 1986.IA.08-14, Folder 5)
      - March 1971, [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-14, Folder 6-7)
      - April 1971, [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-14, Folder 8-9)
      - May 1971, [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-15, Folder 1-2)
      - June 1971, [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-15, Folder 3-4)
      - July 1971, [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-15, Folder 5-6)
      - August 1971, [2 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-15, Folder 7-8)
      - August 1971, [File 2 of 2] (Box 1986.IA.08-15, Folder 8)
      - September 1971, [File 1 of 2] (Box 1986.IA.08-15, Folder 9)
      - September 1971, [File 2 of 2] (Box 1986.IA.08-16, Folder 1)
      - October 1971, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-16, Folder 2-4)
      - November 1971, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-16, Folder 5-7)
      - December 1971, [File 1 of 3] (Box 1986.IA.08-16, Folder 8)